[
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 0",
        "front": "井",
        "back": "정"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 1",
        "front": "刀",
        "back": "도"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 2",
        "front": "促",
        "back": "촉"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 3",
        "front": "初",
        "back": "초"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 4",
        "front": "顧",
        "back": "고"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 5",
        "front": "簡",
        "back": "간"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 6",
        "front": "乳",
        "back": "유"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 7",
        "front": "浮",
        "back": "부"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 8",
        "front": "肺",
        "back": "폐"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 9",
        "front": "尋",
        "back": "심"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 10",
        "front": "囚",
        "back": "수"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 11",
        "front": "抽",
        "back": "추"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 12",
        "front": "樞",
        "back": "추"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 13",
        "front": "醜",
        "back": "추"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 14",
        "front": "亂",
        "back": "란"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 15",
        "front": "掃",
        "back": "소"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 16",
        "front": "所",
        "back": "소"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 17",
        "front": "旋",
        "back": "선"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 18",
        "front": "團",
        "back": "단"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 19",
        "front": "貴",
        "back": "귀"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 20",
        "front": "相",
        "back": "상"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 21",
        "front": "逝",
        "back": "서"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 22",
        "front": "詳",
        "back": "상"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 23",
        "front": "妻",
        "back": "처"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 24",
        "front": "婦",
        "back": "부"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 25",
        "front": "曉",
        "back": "효"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 26",
        "front": "雪",
        "back": "설"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 27",
        "front": "角",
        "back": "각"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 28",
        "front": "嗣",
        "back": "사"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 29",
        "front": "庶",
        "back": "서"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 30",
        "front": "件",
        "back": "거"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 31",
        "front": "孔",
        "back": "공"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 32",
        "front": "後",
        "back": "후"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 33",
        "front": "薄",
        "back": "박"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 34",
        "front": "厚",
        "back": "후"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 35",
        "front": "扇",
        "back": "선"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 36",
        "front": "陽",
        "back": "양"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 37",
        "front": "巾",
        "back": "건"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 38",
        "front": "乞",
        "back": "걸"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 39",
        "front": "過",
        "back": "과"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 40",
        "front": "及",
        "back": "급"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 41",
        "front": "君",
        "back": "군"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 42",
        "front": "休",
        "back": "휴"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 43",
        "front": "舌",
        "back": "설"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 44",
        "front": "器",
        "back": "기"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 45",
        "front": "引",
        "back": "인"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 46",
        "front": "優",
        "back": "우"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 47",
        "front": "瓦",
        "back": "와"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 48",
        "front": "寡",
        "back": "과"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 49",
        "front": "蘭",
        "back": "란"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 50",
        "front": "勤",
        "back": "근"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 51",
        "front": "奇",
        "back": "기"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 52",
        "front": "堅",
        "back": "견"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 53",
        "front": "吉",
        "back": "길"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 54",
        "front": "至",
        "back": "지"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 55",
        "front": "武",
        "back": "무"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 56",
        "front": "戌",
        "back": "술"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 57",
        "front": "止",
        "back": "지"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 58",
        "front": "賦",
        "back": "부"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 59",
        "front": "舞",
        "back": "무"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 60",
        "front": "邑",
        "back": "읍"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 61",
        "front": "泣",
        "back": "읍"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 62",
        "front": "凝",
        "back": "응"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 63",
        "front": "把",
        "back": "파"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 64",
        "front": "吸",
        "back": "홉"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 65",
        "front": "蜜",
        "back": "밀"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 66",
        "front": "玉",
        "back": "옥"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 67",
        "front": "寫",
        "back": "사"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 68",
        "front": "星",
        "back": "성"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 69",
        "front": "走",
        "back": "주"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 70",
        "front": "太",
        "back": "태"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 71",
        "front": "快",
        "back": "쾌"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 72",
        "front": "鶴",
        "back": "학"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 73",
        "front": "笠",
        "back": "립"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 74",
        "front": "葉",
        "back": "엽"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 75",
        "front": "重",
        "back": "중"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 76",
        "front": "酒",
        "back": "주"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 77",
        "front": "酸",
        "back": "산"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 78",
        "front": "酉",
        "back": "유"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 79",
        "front": "醉",
        "back": "취"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 80",
        "front": "冬",
        "back": "동"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 81",
        "front": "紅",
        "back": "홍"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 82",
        "front": "春",
        "back": "춘"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 83",
        "front": "秋",
        "back": "추"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 84",
        "front": "夏",
        "back": "하"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 85",
        "front": "得",
        "back": "득"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 86",
        "front": "幸",
        "back": "행"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 87",
        "front": "偏",
        "back": "편"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 88",
        "front": "飽",
        "back": "포"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 89",
        "front": "純",
        "back": "순"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 90",
        "front": "滅",
        "back": "멸"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 91",
        "front": "表",
        "back": "표"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 92",
        "front": "歸",
        "back": "귀"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 93",
        "front": "豈",
        "back": "기"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 94",
        "front": "何",
        "back": "하"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 95",
        "front": "雖",
        "back": "수"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 96",
        "front": "孰",
        "back": "숙"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 97",
        "front": "疲",
        "back": "피"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 98",
        "front": "比",
        "back": "비"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 99",
        "front": "夕",
        "back": "석"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 100",
        "front": "旦",
        "back": "단"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 101",
        "front": "夜",
        "back": "야"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 102",
        "front": "晝",
        "back": "주"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 103",
        "front": "歌",
        "back": "가"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 104",
        "front": "憤",
        "back": "분"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 105",
        "front": "美",
        "back": "미"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 106",
        "front": "揚",
        "back": "양"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 107",
        "front": "讚",
        "back": "찬"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 108",
        "front": "電",
        "back": "전"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 109",
        "front": "雨",
        "back": "우"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 110",
        "front": "霜",
        "back": "상"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 111",
        "front": "露",
        "back": "로"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 112",
        "front": "責",
        "back": "책"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 113",
        "front": "只",
        "back": "지"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 114",
        "front": "乎",
        "back": "호"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 115",
        "front": "矣",
        "back": "의"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 116",
        "front": "必",
        "back": "필"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 117",
        "front": "悔",
        "back": "회"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 118",
        "front": "逃",
        "back": "도"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 119",
        "front": "述",
        "back": "술"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 120",
        "front": "逆",
        "back": "역"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 121",
        "front": "返",
        "back": "반"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 122",
        "front": "佳",
        "back": "가"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 123",
        "front": "刊",
        "back": "간"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 124",
        "front": "甘",
        "back": "감"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 125",
        "front": "丞",
        "back": "승"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 126",
        "front": "寺",
        "back": "사"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 127",
        "front": "勝",
        "back": "승"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 128",
        "front": "豆",
        "back": "두"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 129",
        "front": "登",
        "back": "등"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 130",
        "front": "吳",
        "back": "오"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 131",
        "front": "危",
        "back": "위"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 132",
        "front": "由",
        "back": "유"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 133",
        "front": "殆",
        "back": "태"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 134",
        "front": "允",
        "back": "윤"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 135",
        "front": "充",
        "back": "충"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 136",
        "front": "完",
        "back": "완"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 137",
        "front": "育",
        "back": "육"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 138",
        "front": "減",
        "back": "감"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 139",
        "front": "淡",
        "back": "담"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 140",
        "front": "浴",
        "back": "욕"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 141",
        "front": "泳",
        "back": "영"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 142",
        "front": "章",
        "back": "장"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 143",
        "front": "央",
        "back": "앙"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 144",
        "front": "恒",
        "back": "항"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 145",
        "front": "方",
        "back": "방"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 146",
        "front": "替",
        "back": "체"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 147",
        "front": "竟",
        "back": "경"
    },
    {
        "id": "chars2 - 148",
        "front": "雙",
        "back": "쌍"
    }
]